<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>http://devm.tech/Hugo-Blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 16:04:52 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://devm.tech/Hugo-Blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Get a custom formatted email message with PR info using Github Actions</title>
      <link>http://devm.tech/Hugo-Blog/get-a-custom-formatted-email-message-with-pr-info-using-github-actions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 16:04:52 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://devm.tech/Hugo-Blog/get-a-custom-formatted-email-message-with-pr-info-using-github-actions/</guid>
      <description>My Workflow I have built my very first Github action from scratch thanks to the Github Actions hackathon by @devteam. The action provides a well-formatted email subject and body using branch name used for Pull Request and other information obtained from the pull request.
I used Javascript to do string processing on the branch name and get a formatted email subject and body with PR info added to it.
The action&amp;rsquo;s inputs and outputs are shown below:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the Jungle</title>
      <link>http://devm.tech/Hugo-Blog/welcome-to-the-jungle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 16:04:52 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://devm.tech/Hugo-Blog/welcome-to-the-jungle/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been two months of me being a part of the software engineers&#39; tribe in the IT jungle, as an Android engineer in an ed-tech startup. Because of the ongoing pandemic, I am working from home like a lot of other tribe members. I never expected my first job to start remotely. I was very excited to start my carrier as a software developer, especially because it would have been an opportunity to move to a new city and explore places - travelling soul I tell you ☹️ - but that didn&amp;rsquo;t happen because of the pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>http://devm.tech/Hugo-Blog/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2015 22:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://devm.tech/Hugo-Blog/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello! everyone. I am Devansh Maurya. Currently, I am pursuing Bachelor of Technology at National Institute of Technology Meghalaya. My branch is Computer Science and Engineering. This being my first blog ever, I will like to introduce myself to you.
Originally, I am from Lucknow, Uttar Pradesh, India. From my childhood, I had a keen interest in physics and astronomy. I always dreamt of working in the field of astronomy. I always thought of pursuing an undergraduate course in physics after completing my school.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
